<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on Timur Bahadir</title>
    <link>https://timur-bahadir.de/tutorial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on Timur Bahadir</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://timur-bahadir.de/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SDL</title>
      <link>https://timur-bahadir.de/tutorial/using_sdl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timur-bahadir.de/tutorial/using_sdl/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I&amp;rsquo;ll share some information needed to use the SDL library with modern CMake. Most guides only use the now deprecated non target_ functions to define include directories.
Installing SDL To make use of SDL in your projects you first need to install it. For that i highly recommend compiling it yourself.
Downloading the SDL source code To compile it yourself, the source code is required. You can either use mercurial like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SFML</title>
      <link>https://timur-bahadir.de/tutorial/using_sfml/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timur-bahadir.de/tutorial/using_sfml/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I&amp;rsquo;ll share some information needed to use the SFML library with modern CMake. This guide is very similar to the one for SDL.
Installing SFML To make use of SFML in your projects you first need to install it. For that i highly recommend compiling it yourself.
Downloading the SFML source code To compile it yourself, the source code is required. You can either use git like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TGUI</title>
      <link>https://timur-bahadir.de/tutorial/using_tgui/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://timur-bahadir.de/tutorial/using_tgui/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I&amp;rsquo;ll share some information needed to use the TGUI library with modern CMake. This guide is very similar to the one for TGUI.
Installing TGUI To make use of TGUI in your projects you first need to install it. For that i highly recommend compiling it yourself.
Downloading the TGUI source code To compile it yourself, the source code is required. You can either use git like this:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>